[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country, known for the worlds longest continuously used written language system, is the subject of study of sinology.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Singapore", "Japan", "Korea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pluto was the ninth planet of the Solar System for 76 years - from its discovery in 1930 until 2006 when it was reclassified as a dwarf planet.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the major source of revenue for the Eilat area?", "correct_answer": "Tourism", "incorrect_answers": ["Agriculture", "Jewelry", "Mining"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Johnny Crawford never received an Emmy nomination.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The large tsetse fly, found in Africa, feeds on what?", "correct_answer": "Blood", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Carrion", "Nectar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is national flower of Venezuela, and its family consists of more than 25 000 species.", "correct_answer": "Orchid", "incorrect_answers": ["Peony", "Camellia", "Magnolia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals is NOT a natural predator of penguins?", "correct_answer": "Polar Bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Leopard Seal", "Stellars Sea Eagle", "Orca (Killer Whale)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Disney movie Cars, Fred is amazed that Mario Andretti knows his name. How does he know it?", "correct_answer": "Its on his license plate.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are related.", "They ran into each other before the race.", "Fred told it to him earlier in the conversation."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do dolphins generally sleep if they are in the wild?", "correct_answer": "with only one brain hemisphere in slow-wave sleep", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "like land mammals", "They dont sleep at all."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Goren solves every case, but this is the name of the A.D.A. who convicts the perps on Law and Order: Criminal Intent.", "correct_answer": "Ron Carver", "incorrect_answers": ["Lionel Hutz", "Mike Cuthrie", "Billy Flynn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Cinderella do with her glass slippers in the Shrek movies?", "correct_answer": "She uses them as weapons.", "incorrect_answers": ["She uses them as musical instruments, making them clink.", "She carries them in her hands.", "She keeps them in a box and never lets anyone touch them."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happened in the pencil world in 1822?", "correct_answer": "The mechanical pencil was invented.", "incorrect_answers": ["The eraser was put onto the pencil.", "Pencils were made with clips to hold onto a  pocket.", "Pencils that wrote in different colors were made."]}]